Name of the application       : Proton
Application type              : Weather app
==============================
DESCRIPTION:
• This is a spontaneous weather application designed using HTML,CSS and JS.
•  It is used to display weather condition including temperature, wind speed, humidity of    any major place in the world at the current moment.
•  It is not designed for forecasting the weather conditions for the next-days.
•  It uses the weather API key from the (openweathermap website) as a source for displaying the result.
